[Theme song]
[Calm music]
You were surprised.
What are you doing with your cell phone?
Will the benefits of civilization be worth it if I use them a little?
I was afraid it would be dangerous, I'm sorry.
What if it's dangerous?
Between partners
We have to share the risk together.
(Chayoung)
I'm really upset!
(Vincenzo)
Lawyer
[Meaningful music]
The real boss of Babel
I figured it out
Really?
yes
Who's the real boss?
(Vincenzo)
Chairman, who are you talking about?
I don't know
[Killer 1’s scream]
Jang Han-seok
Jang Han-seok lives in seclusion in the United States.
You said you were living
no
It was all instructed from behind.
Let's make a call
[Call connection tone]
[Music that heightens the mood]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
(Junwoo)
Uh, senior, here, here, here
[cell phone vibrating sound]
[Call connection tone]
[nervous music]
Didn't you get a call?
yes? jeon…
(Junwoo)
phone
[Laughing]
You didn't come
Oh, I have to call the police, ugh.
Attorney Vincenzo never
He told me not to report it to the police.
Attorney Vincenzo
You'll figure it out.
Put it away
(Junwoo)
yes
Tsk
[sigh]
I don't accept it
[Meaningful music]
That's strange
If you are curious about the results, you will receive it.
That's right
[Oncoming car engine sound]
[tire rubbing sound]
[The car door opens and closes]
[Rhythmic music]
[Meaningful sound effects]
[gunshot]
[The gun is fully loaded]
[Meaningful sound effects]
(Cheolwook)
Hey, who are those people?
Should I say that he is Attorney Vincenzo’s shadow?
(Vincenzo)
Take the three people and go to the warehouse first.
I'll follow you soon
(together)
Yes, lawyer.
(Chayoung)
From the moment I arrived, those two people
I shouldn’t have brought it with me.
I told you to protect the lawyer.
(Vincenzo)
Just in case
Good job, Jang Jun-woo, go first.
I don't like it, I want to stay with my senior.
(Chayoung)
Oh, go quickly! Tsk
(Vincenzo)
Lawyer
I couldn't help it today
Don't be in this situation again
[Meaningful music]
yes, i understand
(Chayoung)
Are you leaving pitifully again?
[Car door slams shut]
[Car starting sound]
You two need to sort things out...
[Exciting music]
(Cheolwook)
The lawyer's car door was open.
I took it out
We will clean up after you.
(Cheolwook)
As if nothing had happened
[laughter]
(Chayoung)
The two of you also to the Plaza people.
You must never say this.
(together)
Yes!
(Vincenzo)
The lawyer and I
Because the killers will drive away
You two, please go back to my car.
- (Cheolwook) Yes
- (Vincenzo) Oh, and
I would like you to clean up the shell casings as well.
[Jusung laughs]
[Jusung puts down the cleaning tool]
don't worry
One shell casing for Korean men
Completely collected
[Slamming the broom]
Loyalty!
[tire rubbing sound]
[nervous music]
(Junwoo)
Ouch!
[angry moaning]
Ah, I thought you caught it, Mr.
[sigh]
No, how can three people get hit at once!
[Grunting]
[Junwoo’s powerful moans]
[angry moaning]
[rattling]
[The killers’ angry groans]
(Chayoung)
Wow, this is just like what you see in the movie.
If I do this, will people die?
This is my first time doing it too.
But more than I thought
I might die sooner
[Meaningful music]
[Knocks the car]
Now, pay attention
Let's settle the bill
(Chayoung)
first
Chairman Jang’s villa burned down
You guys are the ones who killed the researchers, right?
[Button operation sound]
[Car starting sound]
[Car engine sound]
[The killers chuckle]
(Killer 1)
yes we are
(Killer 2)
we are right
[The killers chuckle]
[Button operation sound]
[nervous music]
(Chayoung)
second
Director Gil Jong-moon and prosecutors' investigators also
You guys killed it, right?
(Killer 2)
AC
[Killer 2’s sigh]
[Button operation sound]
[Car engine sound]
(Killer 2)
That's right
(Killer 1)
We did it, we did it, we did it!
(killers)
Stop!
[The killers chuckle]
[Button operation sound]
(Chayoung)
the third most important
Four people committed suicide after lighting a bullet with lightning.
[Meaningful music]
Are you guys like that?
[Killer 1’s sigh]
[Killer 2’s sigh]
- (Killer 2) Yes, yes!
- (Killer 3) We killed him.
(Killer 2)
We killed those people too
That, stop
Please stop, stop!
[The killers chuckle]
[Button operation sound]
[The killers’ painful groans]
[Car engine sound]
[Button operation sound]
(killers)
Stop!
stop!
[The killers chuckle]
Can you feel it now?
What about the pain of those who died in the car?
We just did what we were told
Do as Chairman Jang Han-seok tells you!
[The killers chuckle]
[Button operation sound]
Jang Han-seok
Where are you?
(Killer 1)
I don't know anything except that it's in Korea.
We've never seen each other
Are you sure you are in Korea?
(Killer 1)
Yes, we only accept instructions in our currency
[cell phone vibrating sound]
It was altered when I was talking on the phone.
I can only hear your voice
yes
(Junwoo)
[in a modulated voice]
Don't come to the plaza, go to Yang Cave Bridge.
[nervous music]
To the place where four people were kidnapped
(Killer 1)
yes, i understand
don't lie
You know where Jang Han-seok is.
No, I really don't know.
(Killer 2)
Oh, I really don't know.
I think that's it
Well then it's useless now
Should I get rid of them all?
[Music that heightens the mood]
(killers)
Please save me!
Please save me
(Chayoung)
Even if you die ten times each
They are poor bastards
Usually, after escaping something, humans
I don't want to reflect
Especially for people like you
There is no feeling of reflection
(Killer 1)
Please hand it over to the police!
I will be judged by the law
Judgment of the law?
Who do you like?
Let's go
[Button operation sound]
[surprised moan]
(Killer 3)
Please open the door!
[The killers shout]
[The killers chuckle]
(Killer 3)
Please save me!
[cell phone ringing sound]
(Vincenzo)
Yes, Boss Joe.
[Meaningful music]
Yes, the number I sent you
All you need to do is track the location.
yes
but they are helping us
I get angry every time I see it
Oh, two people?
Just looking at two people
I remember my father’s accident that day.
I understand
These are the people who killed my father.
We'll just have to wait and see.
(Vincenzo)
The day I caught those two people
Do you remember what I said?
When fighting the enemy
Taking advantage of a hunting dog trained by the enemy
It's effective.
I accepted those words
We came this far
(Vincenzo)
When the hounds become useless
The lawyer bought it himself and put it in a cage.
I'll make you throw it
Just wait a moment
Where did you learn how to fight?
(Vincenzo)
From childhood
I took private fighting lessons.
I was a former GIS teacher.
GIS?
Italian special forces
(Chayoung)
[Laughing]
Ah
I thought the form was kind of cool.
[Laugh together]
I really learned to die
(Vincenzo)
A helpless Asian boy
Among the big racist white guys
How to protect yourself
Because there was nothing but force.
[Meaningful music]
What do you plan on doing with the new killers?
These are hunting dogs that don't want to be recycled.
I'm trying to be lenient.
(Vincenzo)
Today’s tolerance is
Less painful than the sins committed
It makes you pay for your sins.
[Exciting music plays]
(people)
Ta-da!
[People are noisy]
(Hongsik)
Stop, stop
(Joosung)
Is it real?
The laundromat owner uses a pair of scissors
Services in one room?
- (in advance) Uh, look.
- (Joosung) Um
(in advance)
Just prick it with scissors
[Miri’s spirit]
[People's elasticity]
(Hongsik)
Oh my
[Heesu’s excited moans]
(Heesu)
When I first saw the owner of our laundromat
I heard you felt something strange.
[Yeonjin responds]
[Hongsik’s awkward laugh]
Wow, it's hot
(Yeonjin)
No, where do you live in an organization?
Are you here?
(Hongsik)
Oh no, what is the organization, ugh
Just over there, well, in my hometown, Chungju
‘Lightning Scissors’, well, that’s what it was called.
[People's elasticity]
Because it's too fast
So you said lightning scissors?
[laughter]
(dropping)
‘Sapgyocheon lightning moktak’
There are also monks who play the moktak quickly.
[People laughing]
(Seokdo)
Oh, I guess I'm lucky
The services that came earlier
Do you know how scary they are?
(Larry Kang)
When did you come in again, huh?
(Sunam)
Gurkha sword tattoo on wrist
You have to be careful
They go to redevelopment sites
People who don't listen are just
All
Because they are people who soak it in
Just came in in the middle of the night
They say they beat me up and killed me.
(Seokdo)
Ugh, by the way
Hey, our self-proclaimed martial artist
When are you going to show me something?
It's a bit of a series of disappointments
(Toto)
Well, well, that
Our pawn shop owner
That one decisive blow
Yeah, I don't think there is one
[Yeonjin’s laughter]
(Yeonjin)
Wow, that's right
Well, at least the neighborhood gangsters
They scold me
Well, there isn't one room in particular.
[People laughing]
(Toto)
Oh, well, by the way, I write
Now our laundromat owner
This fight
Hey, you’re number 1 in the Plaza rankings, huh?
[Hongsik’s awkward moan]
He, Attorney Vincenzo, came in second place.
(Kiseok)
No, no, no, no
However, Attorney Vincenzo
I think you have a bit of a temper tantrum.
Like silkwormwood, chi
[Interesting music]
(Hongsik)
It's a bit awkward to say this with my own mouth
The movements of lawyer Vincen Giocassano
Small tongue, like Stephen Chow
(Cheolwook)
It's not
It's not a big deal
Vincenzo Cassano from Hell
[Cheolwook’s laughter]
[Clinking glasses]
[Each person speaks]
[Calm music]
(Chayoung)
It's so strange
I couldn't have imagined it a few hours ago
I did something incredible
This is how I drink so easily
(Vincenzo)
The lawyer has the personality of a mafia.
(Chayoung)
Let's just drink until 2 o'clock and then we'll be done.
(Vincenzo)
Yes, only until 2 o'clock
(Chayoung)
Huh? It's 3 o'clock
Jjong?
(Vincenzo)
child
4 o'clock, let's only drink until 4 o'clock
There were a lot of snacks left too.
yes
You can't throw away snacks
[Chayoung’s laughter]
[Chayoung sighs]
[Refreshing moan]
Makgeolli
This is a black hole, this is
(Chayoung)
If you drink it, you'll fall into a quagmire
[Laughs]
You know,
I was sorry about the tunnel earlier.
I suddenly hugged you so hard
It was embarrassing, right?
What am I sorry for?
If you're worried, you can do that.
But
[takes a breath]
After holding it, do something
Tsk, it got ambiguous.
(Chayoung)
um
My heart just
My heart is pounding, my heart is pounding
Knockkongdak kongdak kongdak
They just said this
Write, this
Is this because of an emergency?
Otherwise
Because of the lawyer
Is it because I’m excited?
[Chayoung takes a breath]
This needs some testing
(Vincenzo)
Baby, be careful out there, be careful.
(Chayoung)
Um, I'm not drunk.
wake up
Yes?
- wake up
- (Vincenzo) Why?
- (Chayoung) Write!
- Yes
[Puts down the glass]
[Vincenzo clears his throat]
(Chayoung)
I'll only hold you for 10 seconds
Is this some kind of excitement test?
um
Stay still
(Vincenzo)
Yes, I'll stay still.
Just stay still!
yes
[Laughs]
[Soft music]
[Laughs slightly]
[Puzzled breathing]
[Chayoung’s powerful moans]
Ah…
Nope
It was because of an emergency situation earlier.
[Chayoung sighs]
(Chayoung)
Oh my
Oh, I'm very thirsty too.
[Calm music]
[Clears cough]
[sigh]
Tsk, lawyer.
Well, there’s a lot of makgeolli in the warehouse.
I would appreciate it if you could give me some.
[Laughs slightly]
[ECG meter beeping sound]
[The door swings open]
[Welcome sigh]
(Gyeongja)
Are you here?
(Vincenzo)
How are you?
Yes, I was fine.
But you look very tired?
Oh, I have a lot of work to do.
(Gyeongja)
Take it easy
that handsome face
You can't be picky.
(Vincenzo)
Are you eating and taking your medicine well?
Sure
I don't want to get scolded by the lawyer.
[Embarrassed laughter]
A doctor once said
Even 28 years ago
(Vincenzo)
I heard you got better from lung cancer?
[Calm music]
(Gyeongja)
yes
Something with a body
Because I can't change my mind.
Even then, the family
Didn't you have any?
There was
son
(Gyeongja)
[Sighing]
But
Because I accepted my death
I had no choice but to send it.
Where?
very far
A place where my son can grow up happily.
without mom
No matter where you go, you won't be happy.
In the past, to lawyer Hong Yoo-chan,
I heard
Because of the guilt of abandoning my son
(Vincenzo)
He accepts everything, whether it's a false accusation or an illness.
Because that son will be doing well.
Don't feel guilty, get well soon
Don't take it all on your own
Did you know?
yes
I will
Okay, I'll see.
[Myunghee puts down her glass]
(Myunghee)
Write, but still something
Shouldn’t we come up with a solution?
(Junwoo)
don't worry
Vincenzo and Hong Cha-young
You can never find me
Let's put pressure on the three killers
Nothing will come out
(Seunghyuk)
Me, but
To find out the identity of the Chairman
Attorney Choi and I also
Won't they attack me?
[nervous music]
Can you withstand torture well?
- (Seunghyuk) Huh?
- (Junwoo) Huh?
Eh, yes, yes?
Hang it upside down and hit it with electricity.
Hitting my ribs with a bat or something like that.
No, I just can't bear it...
It's coming
[Junwoo thumps the table]
(Junwoo)
Ah! Really
They were the most useful hunting dogs.
It's hard to find dogs like these
(Myunghee)
Unless you really want to hunt and make a stuffed animal.
[Meaningful music]
There is also a way to kick it out of the mountain.
This time we deal with Vincenzo.
How about doing something a little differently?
What how?
Let’s go a little easier.
Vincenzo is a mafia
Isn’t there a hard truth?
(Larry Kang)
It was really cool
(Hongsik)
Don't be like that, shy, kid, whatever.
(Larry Kang and Hong Sik)
- Please teach me too.
- What a big deal.
(Hongsik)
Go somewhere else and do something, hey?
Hey
Attorney Vincen Giocassano
Good morning
Ah, yes
(Hongsik)
Wait a minute
[Interesting music]
If you have something to work on or have money to spare,
Talk about it
Yesterday the boss
Services that came in suddenly
(Larry Kang)
You defeated it
In the past, you used to do
They say it was Chungju lightning scissors.
[Vincenzo’s elasticity]
Good luck
[humorous music]
(Hongsik)
What is it?
No, what kind of reaction is that?
The least surprise
Shouldn’t it be there?
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
(Cheolwook)
Attorney, I have something important to tell you.
[Interesting music]
I am your lawyer's bodyguard.
Could you please write it?
don't do it
They say don't do it.
(Cheolwook)
You don’t have to get that salary.
I want to help the lawyer unconditionally.
boss
yes
I don't need that bodyguard.
You'll need it
(Yeonjin)
[Thumping the desk]
You don't need it!
(Cheolwook)
No matter how much I live without it and the bag strap is short
I want to do something meaningful in the world.
I…
[Cheolwook’s spirit]
[Interesting sound effects]
[Vincenzo’s surprised groan]
With this talent I have
With the help of a lawyer
[humorous music]
I want to beat up the bad guys!
(Yeonjin)
Then, if you get into an accident
Are we cold again?
[Thumping the desk]
Huh? So when are we going to have our child?
(Cheolwook)
It's not a gourd
To our Dallae
That proud father
That's because I want to show you
How old are you?
Like a Hong Kong movie
Save your life!
So do you just live with being bullied every day?
(Cheolwook)
If you step on an earthworm, it doesn't wriggle.
If you step on an earthworm incorrectly
I have to show them that I can become an anaconda!
(Vincenzo)
Oh, I, I, I, I understand.
Let me think about it too...
- (Yeonjin) Don’t even think about it!
- Yes, I understand.
(Cheolwook)
Lawyer
[Vincenzo’s surprised groan]
Please trust us, okay?
(Yeonjin)
You come to work, come out, come out
Lawyer, lawyer
[There is a crunching sound]
[Cheolwook’s scream]
[Yeonjin shouts]
(Cheolwook)
Just put it on my head!
I'm going to run away from home!
[sigh]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
[Vincenzo takes a breath and then exhales]
Ah, yes, Boss Joe.
[Meaningful music]
Yes, I tracked the location of the number you gave me.
There's one big problem
(Chayoung)
So, Jang Han-seok's cannon phone and
Killers' cell phone base station access records
You mean everything has been deleted?
(Vincenzo)
Yes, I went into search.
They said it was in the middle of being deleted.
(Joosung)
No one can delete base station records.
There must have been pressure from the higher ups, I guess.
(Vincenzo)
But fortunately
I found the last access record.
To Jang Han-seok with a killer cell phone
This is the record of the call I made.
Let's take a look at the address.
(Joosung)
‘Yang-dong, Giseong-gu, Seoul’
yangdong
Huh?
Is this the Guldari neighborhood?
Then Jang Han-seok is the one.
So you're saying we've been around?
Wow, where on earth are you hiding, huh?
There really is no such thing as a rat.
Ah, what a sneaky and obnoxious guy.
(Joosung)
Then, if this is the only clue to your cell phone,
How do I find Jang Han-seok?
[Sparkling sound effect]
Do you come here often?
(Kiseok)
Ah, yes
Today too, the teacher served risotto.
(Chayoung)
Well, I keep saying sorry
Because I’m in a meeting today too.
I will eat after finishing.
[Laughing]
yes
(Chayoung)
Thank you
[Exciting music]
(Joosung)
Then I approach through the tunnel.
Let’s check the expected route.
- (Vincenzo) That’s right.
- (Joosung) Yes
(Chayoung)
No, but isn't it too creepy?
watching us
It might have happened
(Joosung)
Yes, at that time
I mean, I've been around.
[Vincenzo’s laughter]
(Vincenzo)
No, but why are there only two?
The lawyer told me not to bring anything with me.
Ah…
No, that's right
Oh, sorry.
I'll bring it next time
- (Vincenzo) Here
- (Kiseok) Ah, yes
(Vincenzo)
thank you
(Kiseok)
yes sorry
[Interesting music]
- Thank you
- (Kiseok) I’m sorry.
(Vincenzo)
thank you
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
- (Vincenzo) No.
- (Kiseok) Sin…
- Thank you so much.
- (Kiseok) Thank you so much
yes, thank you
(Kiseok)
Yes, I, yes
I'm sorry
- I'll go.
- (Vincenzo) Yes, thank you.
Thank you, sorry
- (Vincenzo) Thank you
- (Kiseok) Yes, then
(Vincenzo)
yes, thank you
(Chayoung)
Cell phone location cannot be tracked
(Vincenzo)
There is no way for now.
(Joosung)
If it's like an intelligence agency
I could figure it out in just one shot.
Tsk
[sigh]
[Ancient music]
(Joosung)
Ahn?
[spirited]
[Kiseok imitates the monkey’s cry]
[Vincenzo’s embarrassed groan]
(Vincenzo)
Why, why is it like this?
- (Kiseok) What is this?
- (Vincenzo) Huh? Why this
[Kiseok imitates the monkey’s cry]
[Ancient music]
[spirited]
Let's go
[Kiseok’s spirit]
[Door sound is heard]
(General Affairs Staff)
Are you the head monk?
(dropping)
yes
(General Affairs Staff)
It came from the Defense and Legal Affairs Department of the General Services Administration.
- (Chae Shin) Ah
- (dropping) Ah, yes
(dropping)
hello
But for some reason…
[nervous music]
To complaints regarding the protection of laws on our Jogye Order website,
A complaint has been filed against a drug dealer.
(Chae Shin)
Accusing me?
No, what do you mean?
(General Affairs Staff)
Requesting excessive donations from believers
There are almost no Buddhist ceremonies held.
Yes?
(dropping)
We don't do that
this is a frame
(General Affairs Staff)
sorry
We will begin the investigation according to procedures.
-Excuse me?
- (Chae Shin) No...
(Chae Shin)
No, no…
Ah, there
Hey, no...
Oh my
It's down
(Chayoung)
I need to take some vitamin supplements.
(Joosung)
Huh?
I just need one too
(Chayoung)
Oh, this is for girls.
There is a separate one for men.
[Puts the medicine bottle down]
(Joosung)
Ah…
I see.
You might want to buy it for men.
[Puts the water bottle down]
[Chayoung’s refreshing groan]
(Chayoung)
To find out where Jang Han-seok is,
[Meaningful music]
Idol or Chairman Jang Han-seo
All you have to do is apply pressure.
[takes a breath]
I don't think it'll be easy to break through there.
Contact with Jang Han-seok or know his face
You have to find an unexpected person.
an unexpected person
[surprised moan]
Director?
[Interesting music]
(Vincenzo)
Ah, yes
(in advance)
Today is game day
Are you able to attend?
(Chayoung)
Game day?
(Joosung)
game day
In terms of commercial unity,
I play games once a month
It's also a day for lunch.
Ah…
There was a lot of work last month.
I skipped it
Let’s all be together today
What game are you playing?
It's a mafia game.
[Interesting music]
Yes?
(in advance)
Maybe
Don’t you know the mafia game?
I'm done
(Vincenzo)
Have fun and come back.
[Vincenzo clears his throat]
Lawyer
Please come with me
(in advance)
If the lawyer doesn't go,
I won't go either.
(Vincenzo)
No, that’s…
This is what you want, so please attend.
(Joosung)
If you don't know the rules
I'll explain as I go.
It's very simple
(Vincenzo)
Hey, that's it.
(Chayoung)
Come back for a moment, let's go
(Joosung)
Let's go
Let's brighten up our team's mood.
(Vincenzo and Chayoung)
- I'm really fine, manager.
- Let's go, let's go, have fun, let's come.
- (Joosung) Oh, it’s fun.
- (Vincenzo) Well, I’m really fine.
(Vincenzo)
It's really okay
[Joosung and Chayoung urge]
Ah, that’s it!
[Sound of tapping on table is heard]
Ah
The morning has dawned
[Lonely music]
[Vincenzo clears his throat]
(Hongsik)
Well, just look at this.
Hey, Attorney Vincenzo.
The mafia?
[Vincenzo laughs]
(Miss Miss)
I also think that handsome lawyer is a mafia person.
That's not the mafia
(Heesu)
♪ It seems right, it seems right ♪
Because it's not
Where do I see, is it a mafia?
(Chayoung)
Write
I think they're doing this to be awkward on purpose?
(Kiseok)
Attorney Vincenzo
I don't think it's the mafia
(Toto)
Still, still, still
[Clap your hands]
Ahn is a mafia man, uh, check this out
I can feel your smile
What's wrong
(Seokdo)
Baby, when I see
This lady at the pawn shop is a mafia?
[Interesting music]
Your expression is a bit harsh.
(Yeonjin)
I'm naturally mean
In my view, bye bye boss
Looks like the mafia?
(Larry Kang)
But the owner of Bye Bye Balloon
Who told you to come here?
(Seokdo)
Hey, we just left on our own, whatever.
We are now a shopping family too.
- (Seokdo) Isn’t that right?
- (Sunam) That’s right.
(Cheolwook)
I'm Saeroi Park
This guy looks like the mafia
[Yeonjin’s laughter]
(Sunam)
They say it's salty, sir, honey
Came out to rest after digging a tunnel
They look like North Korean soldiers, Mr.
[Laughing]
Where do I see that I am a North Korean soldier?
[Cheolwook and Yeonjin’s laughter]
(Cheolwook)
reactionary bastard
[People laughing]
Anti-reactionary elements?
(in advance)
Now, now, stop!
Well, you have to vote.
It's night
Now, lie down.
[Interesting music]
[Seokdo’s sigh]
[Kiseok’s laughter]
[People keep knocking on the table]
(Investigator 1)
Excuse me
[in a loud voice]
Excuse me!
(Toto)
Oh, come on, I’m not in business.
(Investigator 1)
Who is Vincenzo Cassano?
It's me, what's going on?
(Investigator 1)
Southeastern District Prosecutors' Office
This is a special international criminal investigation team.
attempted murder and teacher
I'm arresting you for threatening.
[Meaningful music]
You have the right to appoint a lawyer
I have a chance to make excuses
Probation of arrest and detention
You have the right to file a claim in court
What are you saying all of a sudden?
(Investigator 1)
You're the Italian mafia.
It's also a consigliere
(Joosung)
Ah, no, ah, yes, that's us.
We are looking for you
This is a mafia game, a game
Not real, yeah, a game
Arrest me
[Investigators rattle handcuffs]
(Investigator 2)
Wake up
[Yeonjin’s surprised moan]
[People are upset]
(Vincenzo)
Just play the game
I appoint you as my lawyer.
Let's go together
(Larry Kang)
It's a game, isn't it a game?
(Toto)
No, are you really going?
(Chayoung)
I am accompanying this person as his lawyer.
[Toto’s embarrassed groan]
- (Heesu) What is it?
- (Yeonjin) I can’t do it.
(Toto)
Ah, Mr. Ahn, where are you going, huh?
you are the mafia
[Junwoo’s laughter]
(Junwoo)
My cell phone is ringing in my pocket.
[laughter]
He really looked like the main character of a horror movie.
[Junwoo’s laughter]
Oh, really
You almost got into big trouble, brother.
(Junwoo)
no matter what they do
I'll never find out, I'll never find out
[Awkward laughter]
[Junwoo cuts with a sharp knife]
(Chinese book)
Me, brother
(Junwoo)
uh
Babel Pharmaceuticals
Could you please leave it to me?
(Junwoo)
um
Without my interference
Because you want to run everything?
No, no, no…
(Chinese book)
That's not what I'm saying, I...
To my brother so far
I learned so much, I
Yes, I think you can, yes
[Junwoo’s moaning as he thinks]
(Junwoo)
That's right
My younger brother also has an idea.
[laughter]
[dark music]
[The plate shatters]
[Footsteps sound]
[Hanseo’s frightened breathing]
[Sharp sound effect]
[Frightened groan]
I have to draw it out
Are you sure you don't want to think?
[surprised moan]
Brother, you were wrong.
I was wrong, I was wrong
(Junwoo)
No, I have to die.
(Chinese book)
Oh, brother, brother, brother, brother!
So you have a barbell
[Dark sound effect]
[Hanseo’s trembling breathing]
(Chinese book)
Brother, my…
No, I'm sorry, just, just.
Brother, I want to lighten your burden.
It was like that
Sorry, sorry
(Junwoo)
my luggage
Not Babel Pharmaceuticals
[Hanseo’s frightened groan]
It's you
I will never say that again
Sorry, sorry
If you say something like that one more time, really
I'm going to kill you
I'm serious, brother.
[Junwoo’s angry breathing]
[The knife falls with a clink]
[Chuckling]
[Heavy breathing]
[sigh]
You're excited again, Mr.
[Junwoo sighs]
(Chinese book)
From now on
think carefully, carefully
I'll tell you, I'll tell you
I go first
[Hanseo’s frightened groan]
(Junwoo)
go eat breakfast
I lost my appetite because of you
[shaking breathing]
No!
I came out without even knowing it was a mafia.
(Hongsik)
Oh my, I’m embarrassed.
(Heesu)
After watching the movie
The mafia is so cruel
[Meaningful music]
Shooting and killing people with guns
[Yeonjin responds]
I just hung it up in front of my house.
(Yeonjin)
That's right, that's right
[Heesu’s surprised gasp]
(Cheolwook)
what did i say
You said you weren't an ordinary person, right?
(Yeonjin)
Write, but
When you were caught earlier
I told you it was corn salad.
Oh, what does that mean?
That's what CEO Toto said.
Oh, the best mafia
That's what they call it
Corn salad!
It's a very savory and refreshing name.
We are there
To Attorney Vincenzo
Why not seek help?
(Hongsik)
What help?
(Heesu)
Finding gold
The mafia are experts in looking for things like this.
(Yeonjin)
That's right!
We're always wandering around
Hmm, then
Let me also talk about gold.
I'm sure you'll find the answer
Write it, then
Well, each of us, each other like this
They say they'll give you a little bit of money
Let's flirt a little
But you were caught
Is it bad if I go to jail?
(Director Tae)
No, why is the Southeastern District Prosecutors' Office
Are you going to catch Vincenzo?
Idol, Babel, Southeastern District Prosecutors’ Office
Looks like it was worked on
I worked like that and eventually, ugh.
Oh, just leave it alone, it's a pain in the ass.
No
Bring Vincenzo Cassano
We need to take care of it
Oh, okay, what's the benefit?
Just let the Southeast take care of it.
[sigh]
[Splendid music]
Director
Director, don’t you have any bells?
Val?
What are you talking about all of a sudden?
(Kiseok)
The head of international organized crime in Korea is
You are definitely the director.
However, the Southeastern District Prosecutor’s Office
Ignoring the director
I did things on my own
And they don't know anything about international crimes.
Something like a small-bag inspection!
Bringing Vincenzo is
Ensure the status of our information sources
The authority of the director
This is clearly shown to the prosecution.
Director!
(cleaning lady)
That's right, Director!
[The janitor bangs on the window]
[surprised moan]
(Kiseok)
Grazie, ma’am!
Director!
(Cleaning lady and Ki-seok)
Director, Director!
Director…
Bring it to me right now
We manage Vincenzo
[Magnificent music]
Director!
(Cleaning lady and Ki-seok)
Director, Director!
[Prosecutor Park flips through documents]
(Prosecutor Park)
Consiglieri of the Cassano Family, writes
[Meaningful music]
[sigh]
these bodies
Ha, just like that
You did the sword dance well, huh?
No, how many people did you kill?
Arresting people like this without clear evidence
It's illegal
The proof is here, the proof
These photos with Mr. Vincenzo Cassano
The connection is also unclear.
(Chayoung)
And I have some pictures
You can't do this.
(Prosecutor Park)
Write
These aren't just a few pictures.
These days, things like this and that are happening.
You used to hit a lot.
Considering various circumstances
You are subject to deportation
What if there are clear grounds for deportation?
The basis is the basis if I make it.
Is it like that again?
(Vincenzo)
The punishment is set
In fact, it's about making and combining it.
Don't be cocky
(Prosecutor Park)
Chief, take him out.
Look at this, prosecutor.
[The door clicks open]
[Chayoung laughs]
(Investigator 1)
Let's go
[Investigator 3 rattles his handcuffs]
For now, there is
I'll try whatever it takes
It's okay
(Vincenzo)
I'll take care of it
(Prosecutor Park)
Go quickly
(Investigator 1)
Let's go
(Kiseok)
Wait!
[Footsteps sound]
[Rhythmic music]
(Vincenzo)
Ahn?
What is it?
foreign security information source
(Kiseok)
Bureau of International Organized Crime Countermeasures
Italian organized crime response team
Not…
This is team leader Ahn Ki-seok.
[Exciting music]
Awesome
Mr. Vincenzo Cassano
I'm here to guide you
(Prosecutor Park)
No, we caught this person?
Vincenzo Cassano
To cooperate with our sources
(Kiseok)
Please cooperate
The reason is confidential
All evidence obtained here
hand it over to us
Ministry of Justice
This is a handover authorization between our informants.
[Kiseok’s surprised groan]
Oops
Key!
(Prosecutor Park)
Hey, Mr. Lee
[Kiseok rattles his handcuffs]
Let's go, Mr. Vincenzo Cassano.
Attorney Hong Cha-young
[Music that heightens the mood]
[Prosecutor Park’s moans of pain]
(Prosecutor Park)
me, icy, me
[Prosecutor Park’s moans of pain]
(Chayoung)
Oh, sorry
(Prosecutor Park)
I, Mr.
(Junwoo)
From foreign security intelligence sources?
(Myunghee)
yes
Because it is subject to national security surveillance,
They say he took me with him
(Chinese book)
No, what kind of surveillance was there…
Why, why, why, the informant?
I don't know but
something, this
There must be something big, yeah
[Meaningful music]
(Myunghee)
I guess
The identity of the Chairman
I think you need to manage it more tightly.
(Seunghyuk)
yes
The other party is an informant
As for information
They are superior to us.
Because I'm an informant
[Snaps fingers]
That's right, that's right, that's right
[laughter]
(Myunghee)
This is really Vincenzo
Isn’t this some kind of spy thing?
I guess I'm a spy, spy
A spy is a spy
Vincenzo, Vincenzo!
[Lonely music]
(Vincenzo)
So
So you're saying you've been keeping an eye on me?
(Kiseok)
sorry
There was nothing I could do because it was my duty.
Things you've done so far
The identity of Chairman Jang Han-seok
I know everything you want to reveal.
[Vincenzo laughs]
(Chayoung)
But why were you just watching?
(Kiseok)
If you have committed an illegal act
I would have arrested him right away.
But Consiglieri
definition and abbreviation
fought for Buddha
So I stayed still
Oh, Buddha was included, hmm.
What do you plan to do with me next?
Idols, Babel and
Aren't you going to keep fighting?
yes
(Kiseok)
I'm on your side.
I want to help the lawyer
[Interesting music]
(Chayoung)
No, this
Because it's a bit absurd.
Are you really going to help me?
Yes, for the sake of national and social justice.
will help
You know I'm a mafia
Mr. Ahn is from an intelligence agency.
I don't care about that.
(Kiseok)
I respect the Consiglieri.
Why?
Repent all your past
Because you are fighting against absolute evil.
(Chayoung)
Then we too
We will gladly ask for your help.
Let's do it!
(Chayoung)
Call!
(Kiseok)
Instead, there are three conditions:
(Vincenzo)
Oh boy, three more?
(Kiseok)
work
What the lawyer does
Make me an official member
yes
This
(Kiseok)
Telling others who I am
keep it secret
yes
- Hug me just once.
- (Vincenzo) Yes
Yes?
[Interesting sound effects]
I'm embarrassed to say this, but
[humorous music]
Uh, it's really an honor, tsk.
(Chayoung)
They say it's an honor
Give it a try!
(Vincenzo)
What do you do once you do it?
[Chayoung’s urging moans]
[Sad moan]
[Clears cough]
(Vincenzo)
Then, let’s shake hands instead.
[Kiseok’s disappointed groan]
yes
[Kiseok’s powerful moans]
[Vincenzo’s surprised groan]
[Fascinating music]
[Kiseok’s urgent groan]
(Vincenzo)
Please relax your lower body a little.
[Vincenzo’s embarrassed groan]
(Kiseok)
Oh, I
Yes, before I was alive
Meeting the Consiglieri?
[Crying]
Even if I die, Yeohan, Consiglieri
[Meaningful music]
[Kiseok sobs]
these pictures
(Kiseok)
Collected from the Southeastern District Prosecutors' Office
It's evidence
Why are you doing this? Consiglieri
[Italian]
Oh my god!
What's going on?
(Vincenzo)
[Korean]
these pictures
Jang Han-seok sent it to Italy
I'm sure the informant brought it.
This is not information that the district prosecutors can obtain.
If the informant told Jang Han-seok
What if you reported it directly?
The informant was Chairman Jang Han-seok's face.
There is a high probability that you have seen it.
(Kiseok)
[surprised]
Wow, creepy!
[Kiseok’s surprised groan]
All you have to do is find this source of information.
You will be able to approach Jang Han-seok.
Then we need to find it quickly.
Ahn
[Kiseok’s surprised groan]
no
(Vincenzo)
Team Leader Ahn
[surprised moan]
Can you help me with this too?
sure!
Thanks, see you later.
[Rhythmic music]
[Moaning in pain]
(Vincenzo)
thank you so much
Let's go, lawyer.
(Chayoung)
Please take care of me starting today.
[Kiseok’s heavy breathing]
See you at the plaza
(Kiseok)
I, yeah, I always
Behind the Consiglieri
Always, aja, Mamma Mia
[trembling moan]
(Luca)
[Italian]
investigated the consiglieri
Do you mean Korean?
(Vincenzo)
Yeah
See if there are any photos or videos
(Luca)
At the Caruso Hotel
They say they met Giorgio.
Let's take a look at the hotel's CCTV.
(Vincenzo)
ASAP!
(Chayoung)
[Korean]
How long do you think it will take?
(Vincenzo)
Three or four hours is enough.
(Chayoung)
Wow
[Vincenzo takes a breath and then exhales]
[Exciting music is heard]
No…
(Vincenzo)
I'm going
(Chayoung)
Where are you going?
(Vincenzo)
child
(Cheolwook)
Lawyer!
Come this way!
(Vincenzo)
Ah, yes
[Chayoung’s laughter]
[Chayoung hums]
(Chayoung)
Ah, a hero was born in Geumga Plaza.
(Vincenzo)
Oh, really
(Chayoung)
Oh, it's not even a wedding hall. What is this?
[Chayoung’s laughter]
[breathes and then exhales]
[Calm music]
[People cheering]
[Chayoung cheers]
[Hongsik’s heavy breathing]
[Vincenzo’s surprised groan]
[Hongsik makes a quiet sound]
[Vincenzo’s embarrassed groan]
(Hongsik)
great mafia
Corn Salad Vincenzo's
Welcome your safe return.
[People cheering]
You were really blessed with hugs today, right?
(Cheolwook)
we are
We want strong leaders!
[People respond]
A weak leader who only talks
I don't like it
(Toto)
Well, doesn’t the mafia have territories?
[Yeonjin responds]
Please make this a zone
Our corn salad, yes
(Heesu)
Please lead us a little harder
So that we can fight more fiercely
No…
(in advance)
What we need
It's not peace, it's combat power.
[sigh]
(Yeonjin)
Hey, the lawyer
I'm really happy with Mafia Shirt
Fighting, corn salad!
[People cheering]
(people)
Corn salad, corn salad, corn salad!
(Vincenzo)
Me, me, me, me, me
Not corn salad
Consilieri, Consilieri.
[Yeonjin’s embarrassed groan]
(Larry Kang)
No, the toughest mafia
I heard it's called corn salad.
[Toto’s embarrassed groan]
- (Yeonjin) Salad
- (in advance) Hey
[bright music]
(Toto)
No, it's the nose, consiglieri.
I did it, I did it
(Cheolwook)
Anyway!
clap!
[People cheering]
(Joosung)
If you go in and come out
Eating pure white tofu
I'm fine
[People booing]
(Heesu)
I have to eat, I have to eat
(Chayoung)
Take just one bite
- (Heesu) loudly
- (Cheolwook) Ang
(Heesu)
Yes
[People cheering]
(Heesu)
It’s delicious, it’s delicious, right?
Wow, you're eating well
(Seokdo)
Hey, it's a good thing we didn't break up, huh?
We really almost fell behind, didn't we?
(Sunam)
You won't take revenge on us, right?
[People are noisy]
(Miss Miss)
Because my dog looks pitiful
I won't take revenge
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
[Vincenzo’s surprised groan]
(Joosung)
I'm so glad you came out like this.
[Interesting music]
I feel like
Arrested at the police station
Welcoming Kim Doo-han
This is the feeling of the people of Jongno.
Wake up, Doohan.
Duhan, you are the pride of Joseon
Escape? No, wake up, you have to wake up!
you…
- (Vincenzo) Manager
- Yes
Please stop
yes, yes
(Chayoung)
If it's like this
Let’s create a family here.
Geumga Family Corn Salad
Oh my
[cell phone vibrating sound]
[Vincenzo takes a breath and then exhales]
(Vincenzo)
yes
uh
[Speaks Italian]
Huh? Lucada
- (Chayoung) Luca, Luca
- Luca, Luca
[Exciting music]
[Chayoung’s elasticity]
(Chayoung)
The work is done really quickly.
Experts are definitely different
[Elasticity]
(Joosung)
After all, mafia!
[Elasticity]
[Joosung’s applause]
(Joosung)
But
I can tell who this person is just from this video
Can you figure it out?
(Vincenzo)
Can you do a background check?
Hehe
This kind of thing is not even a thing.
How long do you think it will take?
(Kiseok)
Well, 5 hours is enough.
[Chayoung’s elasticity]
Also, the Korean Information Agency
Well, how much tax do we pay?
[The door clicks open]
[Toto hums]
(Toto)
What do you do when you're not taking orders, Ahn?
[Exciting music]
(Kiseok)
Oh, yeah, uh
Truffle and Porcini Spaghetti
It's one
Kimchi Fried Rice
Ah, yes
(Kiseok)
They say you eat kimchi fried rice.
(Toto)
Okay, kimchi fried rice
[The exciting music stops]
No, at some pasta restaurant
Try kimchi fried rice…
[heavy music]
[Answer in Italian]
[Chae-shin's urgent breathing]
(Chae Shin)
There you are, lawyer.
Ah, yes
What's going on?
[Interesting music]
(Chayoung)
The person who posted on the bulletin board
You don’t know who it is?
Yes, anonymous
(Chae Shin)
They say they can’t teach you.
(Chayoung)
This is complete defamation.
If the information is false, compensation for damages may be claimed.
You can make it bigger
(Vincenzo)
If you can't prove it's false
What happens?
(dropping)
We were disciplined and the temple
[nervous music]
It may disappear
(Chae Shin)
It's really so unfair
The head monk really serves only Buddha.
You are a person who works hard.
(Chayoung)
First of all, the person who made the false report
I'll have to find out
[sigh]
[The gun is fully loaded]
[Music that heightens tension]
[gunshot]
[sigh]
(Seunghyuk)
Meeting, Chairman, but
The sound is too loud here right now
Are you okay?
(Chinese book)
This mountain is now a hunting permit area.
You can just shoot this
(Seunghyuk)
Ah
[The gun is fully loaded]
[gunshot]
(Chinese book)
Wow, really
(Seunghyuk)
No, no, but this
The distance is very close now.
This doesn't fit right?
Ah, this
(Chinese book)
Give it a try, try it, try it
[Seunghyuk’s frightened groan]
[Interesting music]
- (Seunghyuk) Me, me?
- (Hanseo) Yes, try it.
(Seunghyuk)
Oh my, my, my, just once
- (Hanseo) Do it quickly
- (Seunghyuk) Yes, yes, once
(Seunghyuk)
Ha, really, this is embarrassing.
[Seunghyuk’s laughter]
(Chinese book)
Try it, try it
(Seunghyuk)
yes
[Seunghyuk clears his throat]
[gunshot]
[Splendid music]
(Chinese book)
What is it?
When I was in the military, I was a full-time shooter.
[Seunghyuk’s laughter]
(Seunghyuk)
The gun is fine.
[Seunghyuk’s laughter]
[Seunghyuk sighs]
[Seunghyuk hums]
[Seunghyuk’s excited moans]
How do you do it?
[Hanseo sighs]
Brother
Not even 1% to me
I have no intention of entrusting the barbell to you.
(Chinese book)
Hey, he said to Vincenzo
Being dealt with every day
What makes you so good
(Seunghyuk)
Well, these days I keep talking to Vincenzo.
I got robbed.
Same thing with that tunnel incident.
So
If the tunnel was caught too
Don't you just die right away?
[Meaningful music]
I'd rather get caught, Mr.
[Seunghyuk rattles his fork]
(Seunghyuk)
Is that what you really mean, Chairman?
(Chinese book)
Boy, rather than being sincere, it’s just…
(Seunghyuk)
I pushed my brother away
Do you want to manage barbell?
Don't say things like that
(Seunghyuk)
But are you worried about what happens next?
How should I run my business without my brother?
don't worry
Strategic support to keep the barbell running smoothly
I'll do enough
[Hanseo’s refreshing groan]
[Hanseo sighs]
Attorney Myeong-hee Choi
Can you support me?
(Seunghyuk)
Attorney Myeong-hee Choi
That adventure
Because it’s a style I don’t like
That's it then
(Chinese book)
But really
Do you think I can do it?
(Seunghyuk)
Of course
I will risk my life to assist the Chairman.
Chairman and me
Knowing I would burn to death
I am not a moth jumping into a fire.
we will be a phoenix
Then, let’s make a road map.
without anyone knowing
[Piano sounds]
[sigh]
[Meaningful music]
[Puts down the mop]
(President Cho)
Lawyer
(Vincenzo)
Something happened at Nan Pharmacist
[nervous music]
Is the boss like that?
Ah, yes
(President Cho)
Yes?
Oh, well, I mean
To get the gold quickly
sorry
I'm more sorry
(Vincenzo)
I'm procrastinating for no reason
I only made the boss frustrated.
(President Cho)
I was careless.
In a hurry
I overdid it
(Vincenzo)
Just like we've done so far
Let’s discuss and decide together.
We're friends
(President Cho)
[in pain]
Yes, yes, lawyer.
I will make sure this never happens again.
(Vincenzo)
It was said that it was a false report on the Jogye Order bulletin board.
Please post again
You can't harm the monks.
I'll post again
That's right
(Vincenzo)
Let's go
yes
[breathes and then exhales]
[The door swings open]
- (Hongsik) Corn Salad Attorney
- (Vincenzo) Oh, yes.
(Hongsik)
Let's talk
[Vincenzo’s embarrassed groan]
What did you say just now?
(Hongsik)
gold
[Meaningful music]
- Gold?
- (Yeonjin) Gold!
(Cheolwook)
Inside this building
Gold worth 12 billion won
I got information that it was hidden
(Heesu)
But
I don't know exactly where it is
I searched the entire building for a whole month.
Who said there was gold?
Is it Gilbert, the local beggar?
Ah…
the poor
Aren’t lawyers experts in this kind of thing?
Does everyone at Plaza know this?
(Yeonjin)
yes
Except for the three straws.
(Heesu)
If you help me
In our house at 11 o'clock
I'll give you a little bit
(Vincenzo)
Hey!
[People moan in surprise]
(Heesu)
Hey! It's an informal way to say something!
(Vincenzo)
not informally
Hey!
There is gold here!
[Interesting music]
There's gold here?
and!
(Cheolwook)
Lawyer
(Vincenzo)
Hey, I'll see all the gold, I, hey!
[People moan in confusion]
(Cheolwook)
Lawyer, hush, hush, wait a minute, kid.
(Vincenzo)
Ah, ah, yeah
Yes, sorry, sorry
- (Cheolwook) It’s okay.
- (Yeonjin) It’s okay.
(Vincenzo)
Oh, by the way
(people)
yes
Why is that gold yours?
Wouldn’t there be a separate owner?
The person who picks it up owns it.
[People laughing]
(Yeonjin)
Right, owner?
(Cheolwook)
Lime is awesome
[People laughing]
(Yeonjin)
It's clear, people
[Vincenzo’s awkward laughter]
[People laughing]
Oh, yeah, yeah, I'll go first, yeah
[nervous music]
[Vincenzo’s angry groan]
[sigh]
Wow, anyone can do whatever they want.
Whoever you like, Mr.
[Moaning in pain]
[sigh]
[System operating sound]
"Search successful"
[Kiseok whistles]
(Joosung)
Huh?
What is this?
[intense music]
[The intense music suddenly stops]
[The door slams shut]
[Moaning in pain]
[Meaningful music]
(Chayoung)
‘Kim Sang-yoon, 41 years old’
'Multinational military company Dioam's
Former Vice President'
'Currently on the European side arms lobbyists and
‘Active as an information book’
[Vincenzo’s groan of approval]
There was a reason I got good information.
But I'm glad I'm in Korea
Now let’s start again, find Jang Han-seok
[cell phone vibrating sound]
(Chayoung)
Why again?
[Meaningful music]
(Junwoo)
I really have to see it today
Is this important information?
(Chayoung)
Don't lie
It's real
Babel Chemical, Babel Pharmaceutical
I don’t think they will compensate the victims.
What?
[Sighing]
Okay
(Chayoung)
I'm going to meet Junwoo.
I really need to find Jang Han-seok
yes
[Car remote control operation sound]
What are you?
[dark music]
(Vincenzo)
It's true that I did it all, but
[Vincenzo clicks his lighter]
I only took out information that was too negative.
Jang Han-seok must misunderstand.
I also donate a lot
There are many people who saved my life.
Will you be the one I kill?
Or will you be the one who saves my life?
just kill it
(Sangyoon)
You want to know the identity of Chairman Jang Han-seok, right?
But I can't say
If you speak...
Even if I live today
I'll be dead in a week
[Clicks open the lighter]
What if I provide you with a way to live?
It's no use
I don't even trust you
[laughter]
[Closes the lighter]
(Vincenzo)
Keeping secrets and maintaining loyalty?
[Vincenzo laughs]
[Vincenzo opens the lighter]
He's a lobbyist.
(Sangyoon)
Russian mafia, terrorists, rebels
I didn't suffer once or twice
I can endure any pain
But I guess you don't know that
There is a limit to pain
In fear
[lighter clicks]
That there are no limits
[intense music]
[The gun is fully loaded]
[Heavy breathing]
[Nervous breathing]
[laughter]
(Vincenzo)
The first game is a draw
second
This time I go first
(Sangyoon)
Now, wait a minute.
[Vincenzo pulls the trigger]
[shaking breathing]
The second game is also a draw
third
[The gun is fully loaded]
This time too, me first
[Sangyoon’s nervous breathing]
[shaking breathing]
[clacking the gun]
The third game was also a draw, the fourth
Stop! Please stop!
I'll tell you everything
(Sangyoon)
Who is Chairman Jang Han-seo?
Idol…
Idol's Lawyer
[Meaningful music]
(Sangyoon)
The name on the idol is
This is Jang Jun-woo.
Show me the information quickly
(Junwoo)
Yeah
no
Give and Take
I'll show you
I also want to give you some information about my senior.
Hey, you're putting such frivolous conditions on it?
(Junwoo)
Don’t do it if you don’t want to deal.
(Chayoung)
Oh my!
Deal!
Tsk
Is this the report that Choi Myung-hee submitted to CEO Han?
I went to the boss's room and took it out of the trash can.
(Junwoo)
Babel Chemicals, Pharmaceuticals officially announced next week
We will withdraw the damage compensation plan.
(Chayoung)
Chairman Jang Han-seo appeared on TV
We agreed to compensate you for everything!
Ah, what a jerk, Mr.
(Junwoo)
Come on!
Now you give me some information too.
[Call connection tone]
(Chayoung)
yes
(Vincenzo)
Just listen to me and don't answer
[nervous music]
Lawyer Jang Jun-woo
This is Jang Han-seok.
(Vincenzo)
I was a lawyer's junior and intern.
Jang Jun-woo
It was Jang Han-seok.
[Meaningful music]
What are you going to do?
Are you going to follow the plan?
[Junwoo’s excited moans]
[Junwoo sighs]
[Junwoo is humming]
[makes a loud mouth sound]
[Button operation sound]
[Puts down the remote control]
[Clears cough]
[Refreshing moan]
(Vincenzo)
Junwoo Jang
[nervous music]
(Junwoo)
Attorney Vincenzo?
[Dark sound effect]
[Music that heightens tension]
[surprised moan]
kneel down
What's happening all of a sudden?
knee
Kneel down
[Embarrassed groan]
(Junwoo)
Ah, why are you doing this?
Tell me something, okay?
(Vincenzo)
stop now
Jang Han-seok
[Meaningful music]
IC
caught
How did they know?
It's possible to hide the fire
It's hard to hide the smoke
(Junwoo)
Even though I turned the hood hard
Looks like there's some smoke left?
Say your last prayer
I don't pray or anything
[Music that heightens the mood]
kill it quickly
You mafia bastard
[nervous music]
[laughter]
if you want
[Music that heightens tension]
[gunshot]
[Magnificent music]
[Rhythmic music]
(Myunghee)
I think you have to make a decision now.
(Vincenzo)
The war has begun
(Chayoung)
Babel Group's six charges
I heard you're ready to file a complaint.
(Seunghyuk)
By then, Korea will be completely turned upside down.
(Chinese book)
I do as you wish
I will help you die
Leave me and Babel alone.
(Myunghee)
If you hold the line wrong
That will be the rope that hangs you.
(Vincenzo)
I'm really going to kill you
If you're scared, run away
I'll follow you again
Subtitle: Kwon Jeong-won